A Guide to the Edgar B. Young papers FA109
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Lincoln Center, Inc., 1952-1980 (1956-1976); 1956-1976; 1; 26.48 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box, and 1 flat file folder; 69 Boxes 27.6 cubic feet
  - Financial Administration, 1956-1972; 6
    - Reports - Financial and Concept Planning, 1959-1963 (Box 30, Folder 343)
    - Reports - Financial and Concept Planning, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 344)
    - Reports - Financial and Concept Planning, 1969-1971 (Box 30, Folder 345)
    - Summaries and Projections, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 346)
    - Summaries and Projections, January-April 1969 (Box 30, Folder 347)
    - Summaries and Projections, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 348)
  - Fundraising, 1956-1973; 7
    Lincoln Center, Inc., as a nonprofit institution with no accumulated financial reserves and no corporate or commercial means of financing, originally envisioned a private-sector fundraising campaign seeking the support of individual donors and organizational grants. Due to expansion of the project and rising capital costs, Lincoln Center also sought city, state, and federal government funding, but the private sector remained the source of a majority of the funding, and acquiring such funds remained a top priority. This subseries documents the private fundraising campaign. The largest organization grants were submitted by the Ford Foundation and the Rockefeller Foundation as well as the Avalon Foundation. Monumental personal pledges were received early on from John D. Rockefeller Jr. and John D. Rockefeller 3rd, which helped to solidify the ultimate success of the project as well as spur the Lincoln Center Campaign toward greater and more diversified support. Also noteworthy are the gifts by Vivian Beaumont Allen and Alice Tully for the theaters that bear their respective names.
    - Anonymous Gift of Real Estate, 1958-1959 (Box 30, Folder 349)
    - Anonymous Gift of Real Estate, 1960-1961 (Box 30, Folder 350)
    - Austrian Gift, 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 351)
    - Avalon Foundation, 1957-1961 (Box 31, Folder 352)
    - Mrs. V. Beaumont Allen, 1957-1963 (Box 31, Folder 353)
    - Capital Fund, Finances, Brochures, undated (Box 31, Folder 354)
    - Capital Fund, Finances, Brochures, 1957-1969 (Box 31, Folder 355)
    - Carnegie Corporation, 1958-1962 (Box 31, Folder 356)
    - Consolidated Corporate Fund Drive, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 357)
    - Consolidated Corporate Fund Drive, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 358)
    - Estate of Hazel Hopkins Ford, 1962; 1963 (Box 31, Folder 359)
    - Ford Foundation, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 360)
    - Ford Foundation, 1958-1962 (Box 31, Folder 361)
    - Ford Foundation, 1963-1969 (Box 31, Folder 362)
    - General Files, September 1956-February 1958 (Box 31, Folder 363)
    - General Files, March 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 364)
    - General Files, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 365)
    - General Files, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 366)
    - General Files, January-June 1962 (Box 32, Folder 367)
    - General Files, July-December 1962 (Box 32, Folder 368)
    - General Files, January-July 1963 (Box 32, Folder 369)
    - General Files, August 1963-March 1964, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 370)
    - Estate of John L. Given, Jr., 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 371)
    - The John A. Hartford Foundation, Inc., 1957-1964 (Box 32, Folder 372)
    - James Foundation of New York, Inc., 1958-1963 (Box 32, Folder 373)
    - Keiser, David M., 1958-1963 (Box 33, Folder 374)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - Campaign Committee (Mr. Francis), 1957-May 1958 (Box 33, Folder 375)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - Campaign Committee (Mr. Francis), July 1958-May 1959 (Box 33, Folder 376)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - Campaign Committee (Mr. Francis), June 1959-November 1960 (Box 33, Folder 377)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - Development Committee, April 1963-1965 (Box 33, Folder 378)
      See also Box 34, Folder 388: Lincoln Center Campaign - General, 1962-March 1963 (1972).
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - General Files, January-September 1957 (Box 33, Folder 379)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - General Files, October 1957-February 1958 (Box 33, Folder 380)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - General Files, March-December 1958 (Box 33, Folder 381)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - General Files, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 382)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - General Files, January-May 1960 (Box 33, Folder 383)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - General Files, June-November 1960 (Box 34, Folder 384)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - General Files, 1961 January-March 21 (Box 34, Folder 385)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - General Files, 1961 March 22-May (Box 34, Folder 386)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - General Files, 1961 June-October (Box 34, Folder 387)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - General Files, 1962-1963 March (Box 34, Folder 388)
      See also Box 33, Folder 378: Lincoln Center Campaign - Development Committee.
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - International Fund, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 389)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - Seat Endowment Campaign, 1961-1964 (Box 34, Folder 390)
    - The Lincoln Center Fund, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 391)
    - The Lincoln Center Fund, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 392)
    - The Lincoln Center Fund, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 393)
    - The Lincoln Center Fund, 1970-1972 (Box 34, Folder 394)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association Pledges, 1956-1961 (Box 34, Folder 395)
    - New York Foundation, Inc., 1956-1959 (Box 35, Folder 396)
    - Mrs. John T. Pratt, April-May 1958 (Box 35, Folder 397)
    - Public Participation Campaign, 1959 September-1960 March 7 (Box 35, Folder 398)
    - Public Participation Campaign, 1960 March 8-September (Box 35, Folder 399)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 6.
    - Mr. John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1956-1960 (Box 35, Folder 400)
    - Mr. John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1962-1971 (Box 35, Folder 401)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - General Files, 1955-1957 (Box 35, Folder 402)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - General Files, 1958-June 1960 (Box 35, Folder 403)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 7.
    - Rockefeller Foundation - General Files, July 1960-1963 (Box 35, Folder 404)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Report of Progress, 1967 November 6-1968 (Box 35, Folder 405)
    - Sloan Foundation, 1956-1960 (Box 35, Folder 406)
    - Special Purpose Gift Fund, 1962-1971 (Box 35, Folder 407)
    - Miss Alice Tully, 1958-1962 (Box 35, Folder 408)
  - Kirstein, Lincoln, 1953-1959; 8
    This subseries contains the Lincoln Center files of Lincoln Kirstein, managing director of the New York City Ballet. He was an active participant in the Exploratory Committee for a Musical Arts Center and played a vital role in the establishment and creation of Lincoln Center. The Day and Zimmerman Feasibility Report of 1956 and Kirstein's mid-1950s outgoing correspondence illuminate the organization's early issues and policy formation decisions.
    - Correspondence (Outgoing) and Memoranda, 1955-1956 (Box 35, Folder 409)
    - Correspondence (Outgoing) and Memoranda, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 410)
    - Correspondence (Outgoing) and Memoranda, 1957-1959 (Box 36, Folder 411)
    - Exploratory Committee for a Musical Arts Center - Conferences, 1956 February 17-June 7 (Box 36, Folder 412)
    - Exploratory Committee for a Musical Arts Center - General Files, undated (Box 36, Folder 413)
    - Exploratory Committee for a Musical Arts Center - General Files, 1953-1956 February 13 (Box 36, Folder 414)
    - Exploratory Committee for a Musical Arts Center - General Files, 1956 March-June 19 (Box 36, Folder 415)
    - Exploratory Committee for a Musical Arts Center - Meetings Minutes, 1955-1956 April (Box 36, Folder 416)
    - Exploratory Committee for a Musical Arts Center - Meetings Minutes, May-November 1956 (Box 36, Folder 417)
    - Lincoln Center By-Laws, Incorporation, Agreement, 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 418)
    - Lincoln Center Board Minutes, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 419)
    - Lincoln Center Campaign - Weekly Memos from Clarence Francis, 1957-1959 (Box 36, Folder 420)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - General Files, undated (Box 36, Folder 421)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - General Files, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 422)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - General Files, January-August 1957 (Box 36, Folder 423)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - General Files, September-December 1957 (Box 37, Folder 424)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - General Files, January-July 1958 (Box 37, Folder 425)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - General Files, September-December 1958 (Box 37, Folder 426)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - General Files, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 427)
    - Lincoln Square - Donations and Donors - General Files, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 428)
    - Lincoln Square - Donations and Donors - Potential Interest Lists - The Arts Center Program at Columbia University, March 1956 (Box 37, Folder 429)
    - Lincoln Square - General Files, n.d.; 1956-July 1958 (Box 37, Folder 430)
    - Lincoln Square - General Files, November 1958-April 1959 (Box 37, Folder 431)
    - Miscellany, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 432)
    - Press Releases, News Clippings, Speeches, Publications, n.d.; 1955-1957 (Box 37, Folder 433)
    - Press Releases, News Clippings, Speeches, Publications, January-August 1958 (Box 37, Folder 434)
    - Press Releases, News Clippings, Speeches, Publications, September-December 1958 (Box 38, Folder 435)
    - Press Releases, News Clippings, Speeches, Publications, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 436)
    - Report - Day & Zimmerman, Inc. Feasibility Report - pp. 1-70, 1956 December 31 (Box 38, Folder 437)
    - Report - Day & Zimmerman, Inc. Feasibility Report - pp. 71-end, 1956 December 31 (Box 38, Folder 438)
    - Report - Day & Zimmerman, Inc. Feasibility Report - Addenda, 1956 December 31 (Box 38, Folder 439)
    - Report - Day & Zimmerman, Inc. Feasibility Report - Appendices, IV-A - V-5, 1956 December 31 (Box 38, Folder 440)
    - Report - Day & Zimmerman, Inc. Feasibility Report - Appendices, V-F - end, 1956 December 31 (Box 38, Folder 441)
  - Planning and Construction, 1956-1978; 9
    The largest portion of the collection documents the planning and construction of each building in the Lincoln Center complex, as well as various aspects of the Lincoln Center Urban Renewal Project including the relocation of original residents, the purchase and demolition of the Kennedy building, and the expansion of the Juilliard School to encompass the High School of Commerce site. The files of the Building Committee and its various Subcommittees are also available.
    Wallace K. Harrison served as the design architect for the Lincoln Center complex, developing and executing the overall site plan. Planning and construction of each of the Lincoln Center buildings was a separate and contractually independent project with its own custom architectural and engineering specifications, its own design architect and construction firm, and its own budget and completion schedule. The design architects for each individual building within the complex are: Philharmonic Hall - Max Abramovitz; Metropolitan Opera House - Wallace K. Harrison; New York State Theater - Philip Johnson; Vivian Beaumont Theater - Eero Saarinen; Library/Museum (physically connected to the Vivian Beaumont Theater) - Gordon Bunshaft; Juilliard School and Alice Tully Hall - Pietro Belluschi. Various acoustic and stage alterations following building completion are also documented including the Bolt, Beranek and Newman acoustics study, and subsequent alterations, of Philharmonic Hall.
    Another vital aspect of the Lincoln Center project is the negotiations, agreements, and public funding obtained, from the city and state of New York and the federal government. Of particular note is the agreement by Lincoln Center to host the performing arts activities of the New York World's Fair (1964-1965) and the subsequent state funding obtained for what became the New York State Theater. As a result of this agreement Lincoln Center was contractually obligated to complete the New York State Theater and its Promenade, as well as several other portions of the complex, for the World's Fair.
    - Architects - Architects Panel, 1959-1964 (Box 38, Folder 442)
    - Architects - Architects Panel, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 443)
    - Architects - General Files, 1957-September 1959 (Box 38, Folder 444)
    - Architects - General Files, October 1959-1962 (Box 38, Folder 445)
    - Band Shell - Architectural Models and Sketches, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 446)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 8.
    - Band Shell - General Files, 1961-1969 (Box 39, Folder 447)
    - Building Committee - General Files, November 1957-February 1958 (Box 39, Folder 448)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 9.
    - Building Committee - General Files, March-May 1958 (Box 39, Folder 449)
    - Building Committee - General Files, June-October 1958 (Box 39, Folder 450)
    - Building Committee - General Files, November-December 1958 (Box 39, Folder 451)
    - Building Committee - General Files, January-February 1959 (Box 39, Folder 452)
    - Building Committee - General Files, March-April 1959 (Box 39, Folder 453)
    - Building Committee - General Files, 1959 May 4-20 (Box 39, Folder 454)
    - Building Committee - General Files, 1959 May 25-28 (Box 39, Folder 455)
    - Building Committee - General Files, June-July 1959 (Box 39, Folder 456)
    - Building Committee - General Files, September-December 1959 (Box 39, Folder 457)
    - Building Committee - General Files, January 1960 (Box 39, Folder 458)
    - Building Committee - General Files, February-April 1960 (Box 39, Folder 459)
    - Building Committee - General Files, May-July 1960 (Box 39, Folder 460)
    - Building Committee - General Files, September-October 1960 (Box 39, Folder 461)
    - Building Committee - General Files, November-December 1960 (Box 39, Folder 462)
    - Building Committee - General Files, February-June 1961 (Box 39, Folder 463)
    - Building Committee - General Files, July-November 1961 (Box 39, Folder 464)
    - Building Committee - General Files, January-April 1962 (Box 39, Folder 465)
    - Building Committee - General Files, May-September 1962 (Box 39, Folder 466)
    - Building Committee - General Files, October-December 1962 (Box 40, Folder 467)
    - Building Committee - General Files, January-March 1963 (Box 40, Folder 468)
    - Building Committee - General Files, April-December 1963 (Box 40, Folder 469)
    - Building Committee - General Files, January-June 1964 (Box 40, Folder 470)
    - Building Committee - General Files, September-December 1964 (Box 40, Folder 471)
    - Building Committee - General Files, January-August 1965 (Box 40, Folder 472)
    - Building Committee - General Files, September 1965-February 1966 (Box 40, Folder 473)
    - Building Committee - General Files, March-December 1966 (Box 40, Folder 474)
    - Building Committee - General Files, January-February 1967 (Box 40, Folder 475)
    - Building Committee - General Files, March 1967-January 1968 (Box 40, Folder 476)
    - Building Committee - General Files, March-November 1968 (Box 40, Folder 477)
    - Building Committee - General Files, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 478)
    - Building Committee - General Files, 1971; 1973 (Box 40, Folder 479)
    - Building Committee - Juilliard Subcommittee, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 480)
    - Building Committee - Juilliard Subcommittee, 1961-1963 (Box 40, Folder 481)
    - Building Committee - Juilliard Subcommittee, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 482)
    - Building Committee - Library/Museum Subcommittee, 1960-1962 (Box 40, Folder 483)
    - Building Committee - Metropolitan Opera House Subcommittee, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 484)
    - Proposed Time Schedule for Metropolitan Opera. Lincoln Center., 1960 January 26; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 2)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 40, Folder 484
    - Building Committee - Metropolitan Opera House Subcommittee, 1961-1962 (Box 40, Folder 485)
    - Building Committee - Metropolitan Opera House Subcommittee, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 486)
    - Building Committee - New York State Theater Subcommittee, February-June 1963 (Box 40, Folder 487)
    - Building Committee - New York State Theater Subcommittee, July-October 1963 (Box 41, Folder 488)
    - Building Committee - New York State Theater Subcommittee, November 1963-January 1964 (Box 41, Folder 489)
    - Building Committee - New York State Theater Subcommittee, February-May 1964 (Box 41, Folder 490)
    - Building Committee - Philharmonic Hall Subcommittee, February-June 1960 (Box 41, Folder 491)
    - Building Committee - Philharmonic Hall Subcommittee, July 1960-March 1962 (Box 41, Folder 492)
    - Building Committee - Repertory Theater Subcommittee, 1960-1964 (Box 41, Folder 493)
    - Building Committee - Vivian Beaumont Theater - Library Museum Subcommittee, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 494)
    - Church-State Issue (Court Case), September 11-October 1, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 495)
    - Church-State Issue (Court Case), October 17-November 19, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 496)
    - Church-State Issue (Court Case), December 1957-July 1958 (Box 41, Folder 497)
    - Church-State Issue (Court Case), August 1958-May 1959 (Box 41, Folder 498)
    - Commissary, 1962 January 8-1967 April 13 (Box 41, Folder 499)
    - Commissary, 1967 April 20-1969 (Box 41, Folder 500)
    - Construction - General Files, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 501)
    - Construction - General Files, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 502)
    - Construction - General Files, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 503)
    - Construction - General Files, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 504)
    - Construction - General Files, March-August 1966 (Box 41, Folder 505)
    - Construction - General Files, September-December 1966 (Box 41, Folder 506)
    - Construction - General Files, February-May 1967 (Box 41, Folder 507)
    - Construction - General Files, June 1967 (Box 41, Folder 508)
    - Construction - General Files, July 1967-March 1968 (Box 41, Folder 509)
    - Construction - General Files, September 1968-April 1969 (Box 41, Folder 510)
    - Construction - General Files, May-July 1969 (Box 42, Folder 511)
    - Construction - General Files, August-October 1969 (Box 42, Folder 512)
    - Construction - General Files, November 1969-April 1970 (Box 42, Folder 513)
    - Construction - General Files, January-March 1970 (Box 42, Folder 514)
    - Construction - General Files, April 1970-March 1972 (Box 42, Folder 515)
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City, October-December 1956 (Box 42, Folder 516)
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City, February-April 1957 (Box 42, Folder 517)
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City, May-September 1957 (Box 42, Folder 518)
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City, October 1957-February 1958 (Box 42, Folder 519)
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City, April-November 1958 (Box 42, Folder 520)
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City, 1959 January-July 22 (Box 42, Folder 521)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 10.
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City, 1959 July 27-August 13 (Box 42, Folder 522)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 11. Architectural material has been removed and is housed separately.
    - Lincoln Center Site Plan., 1959 August 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 2)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 42, Folder 522
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City, 1959 August 24-1960 July 1 (Box 42, Folder 523)
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City, 1957-1961 (Box 42, Folder 524)
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City - Appendix File 2, 1959 July 24 (Box 42, Folder 525)
    - Lincoln Center Site Plan., 1959 July 16; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 2)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 42, Folder 525
    - Lincoln Center "Plaza Level 1" Layout., 1958 July 22; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 2)
    - Federal Government - Negotiations re: Site and Contract with New York City - Appendix File 3, August 3, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 526)
    - Lincoln Center "Plaza Level 1" Layout., 1958 July 22; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 43, Folder 526
    - Lincoln Center Site Plan., 1959 August 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
    - Fountain, March 1962-March 1963 (Box 43, Folder 527)
    - Fountain, June-November 1963 (Box 43, Folder 528)
    - Fountain, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 529)
    - Fountain, 1965; December 1966; January 1967 (Box 43, Folder 530)
    - Garage Complex - Federal Grant-in-Aid, 1957-1958 (Box 43, Folder 531)
    - Garage Complex - Federal Grant-in-Aid, March-September 28, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 532)
    - Plan of Lincoln Center Property. With Financial Report attached., 1959 September; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 43, Folder 532
    - Photocopy of Garage Plan at Lincoln Center. "Enclosure 3A.", 1959 September; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1); oversized and folded. (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
    - Garage Complex - Federal Grant-in-Aid, September 30-December 1, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 533)
    - Garage Complex - Federal Grant-in-Aid, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 534)
    - Garage Complex - Federal Grant-in-Aid, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 535)
    - Plan for Lincoln Center Plaza Upper Level Plan. With Correspondence., 1961 February; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
      Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 43, Folder 535
    - Photocopy of Plan for Lincoln Center Plaza Lower Level Plan. With Correspondence., 1961 February; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
    - Garage Complex - Federal Grant-in-Aid, 1966-1971 (Box 43, Folder 536)
    - Garage Complex - Negotiations with New York City and Housing and Development Administration, 1964-February 8, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 537)
    - Garage Complex - Negotiations with New York City and Housing and Development Administration, February 11, 1971-1973 (Box 43, Folder 538)
    - Garage Complex - Negotiations with New York City and Housing and Development Administration - Nov 14, 1968 Report by Powers (Box 43, Folder 539)
    - Handicapped Facilities in Buildings - General Files, 1960-1972 (1973) (Box 43, Folder 540)
    - Handicapped Facilities in Buildings - Report, January 1967 (1973) (Box 43, Folder 541)
      Architectural Barriers Committee of Metropolitan New York: Report on Lincoln Center Tour.
    - Insurance, 1967 (1971) (Box 43, Folder 542)
    - Insurance, 1968-May 1969 (1971) (Box 43, Folder 543)
    - Insurance, July 1969-December 1972 (1971) (Box 43, Folder 544)
    - Insurance, March 1973 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 545)
    - Joint Venture, October-December 1958 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 546)
    - Joint Venture, 1959-1960 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 547)
    - Joint Venture, March 1961-August 1, 1962 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 548)
    - Joint Venture, August 7-December 1962 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 549)
    - Joint Venture, February 1962 (1971) (Box 44, Folder 550)
    - Juilliard Building - Acoustics - General Files, 1962-1972 (1970) (Box 44, Folder 551)